Villie Pol

UX Designer - Design Researcher Sydney, NSW

About Me

I'm a User Experience Designer, passionate about research and problem solving.

Working previously as a Nutritionist, I built great relationships with patients and was able to deeply understand their behavior and motivations, and found solutions for each of their requirements to achieve the discussed goals.

Work Experience

Guardian Childcare & Education JAN 2020 - JAN 2022 Chef/Nutritionist -

- · Responsible for developing cooking classes and immersive cooking experiences;
- · Built relationships with parents and children creating a safe environment and a fun experience for the children; Utilising empathy research I guided kids and parents through a healthier life style.

Mika Events - Luxury Picnics Founder -NOV 2020 - DEC 2021

As a founder, I conducted Market Research, Competitive and Comparative Analysis and interviews to understand the market and client needs.

I managed 3 team members, organised schedules, communicated with stakeholders.

Industry Skills

Professional Skills

- Discover: UX Research
- Define: Synthesis
- Surveys
- Competitive &

Comparative Analysis

- Contextual Inquiry
- User Interviews
- Field Studies
- User observation
- Market analysis
- Affinity Mapping
- User scenarios
- Journey Mapping
- Personas & archetype
- User flows
- Information Architecture

Contact

- 0426 020 087
- millepolicamilo@gmail.com
- https://milliepoli.com/
- in https://www.linkedin.co/in/kamille-poli/

Education History

General Assembly - Sydney, NSW

UX Design Immersive

Full-time UX immersive course with 500+ hours of

Jan 2022 -**April 2022** professional workshops.

Developed in-class projects practising the design thinking process and utilising design tools

Estacio de Sa University - Brazil

Bachelor Degree in Nutrition

Jan 2010- Nutrition and dietetics skills, JUL 2014 patient interviews, psychology

and storytelling.

Achievements

3 times winner "Guardian Gstar" Employee of the month at Guardian Childcare & Education

Design Tools

FIGMA MIRO SKETCH Trello

Ideation: Solution & Iteration

- Problem Solving
- Design Studio
- Sketchina
- Wireframe & Wireflows
- Usability Testing and A/B testing
- Prototyping

Deliver: Communicating with Client

- Presenting project
- Storytelling
- Feedback loops
- Product Analytics
- Working with a team